Now, add 140 for me, 120 for you...
- One-twenty?
- Oh, I'm sorry, did I insult you?
(Sheldon:)Is your body mass
somehow tied into your self-worth?
(Penny:)Well, yeah.
(Leonard:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, that gives us a total weight of,
let's say, 4400 pounds.
(Penny:)Let's say 4390.
(Penny:)Fine.
We're traveling forward at...
Good Lord... 51 miles an hour.
(Sheldon:)Let's assume that your brakes are new
and the calipers are aligned.
(Sheldon:)By the time we come to a stop...
(Sheldon:)...we'll be occupying the same space
as that Buick.
(Sheldon:)An impossibility that nature will quickly
resolve into death, mutilation and...
(Sheldon:)Oh, look,
they built a new putt-putt course.
SHELDON:
This is great.
(Sheldon:)Look at me.
I'm in the real world of ordinary people...
(Sheldon:)...just living their ordinary,
colorless, work-a-day lives.
(Leonard:)- Thank you.
- No, thank you.
(Sheldon:)And thank you, ordinary person.
Hey, you wanna hear an interesting thing
about tomatoes?